隐世狼女前情提要
Previously on "Bitten"...
你要么现在就变身
You can change right now
要么就为这个女人的死负责
or you can be responsible for this lady's death.
克拉拉・沙利文曾是我们最优秀的女巫之一
Clara Sullivan was one of our brightest witches.
却克服不了内心的阴暗
She always had a dark side.
瞧瞧你让我们陷入何种境地了
What have you gotten us into?
这都是你造成的 他出现了 是不是
You got us into it. He's out there, isn't he?
预言说 他会杀了你
He's about to kill you. The prophecy.
亚雷斯塔准备设法杀了所有女巫
Aleister is going to cast a spell to kill all witches.
他想把我的血液注射给你
He wants to inject my blood into you.
叮咚 巫婆死了
Ding-dong, the witch is dead.
萨凡纳 我可以通过你和露丝对话吗
Savannah, can I talk to Ruth through you?
我是埃琳娜 我们在魁北克的某处
This is Elena.We're somewhere in Quebec.
我想以前是某种军事基地
I think it's some type of former military base.
不 我需要你
No! I'm going to need you
做一切有可能
to do whatever possible
帮助我们鉴别那个化合物的事
to help us identify that compound.
你打算什么时候把真相告诉佩吉
When were you going to tell Paige the truth?
亚雷斯塔是你儿子
That Aleister is your son?
放我走
Let me go!
释放你的恐惧 把它传递给她
Let your fear go. Send it out to her.
你现在充满力量
You are all-powerful.
今天 你就完全是个女巫了
Today, you are a full witch.
三十年前 康乃迪克州 温莎市
露丝 你来干什么
Ruth? What are you doing here?
我在回波士顿的路上
I was on my way back to Boston.
你是五十英里之内唯一的女巫团员
You're the only Coven member within 50 miles.
我不知道还能去哪
I didn't know where else to go.
我需要你的帮助 我的羊水破了
I need your help. My water broke.
进来
Get inside.
三分钟
Three minutes.
深呼吸 露丝
Breathe, Ruth!
集中注意力 深呼吸
Focus on that and breathe.
你还记得让人心平气和的咒语吗
Do you remember the ataraxia spell?
用它
Use it.
克拉拉
Clara?
用力 露丝 用力
Push, Ruth! Push!
继续用力 继续用力
Keep pushing! Keep pushing! Keep pushing!
你可以的 好吗 可以的...
You can do it, okay? Okay...
你为什么没让我看看她
Why won't you show her to me?
露丝 这个宝宝有点问题
Ruth, there's a problem with the baby.
什么
What?
是个男孩
It's a boy.
不 不可能的
No, that's impossible.
哦 这下有意思了
Oh, this is rich.
露丝・温特伯恩  下一任女巫团首领
Ruth Winterbourne, next in line for Coven leader,
生下来了一个男婴
gives birth to a male child.
你来解决这事儿
You're going to fix this.
你来除掉它
You're going to get rid of it.
好好想想 这是你的难题 露丝
Think again. This is your problem, Ruth.
- 你卖了多少法术了 - 你不会的
- How many spells have you sold? - You wouldn't.
女巫协会会毁了你的护身符的
The Coven will crush your talisman.
你会被剥夺一切
You'll be stripped of everything.
你要告诉大家这是一个死胎
You're going to tell the Coven that it was a stillborn.
但是首先...
But first...
你要来解决一下我的错误
you're going to get rid of my mistake.
你想让我干什么
What do you want me to do?
你知道你该怎么做
You know what you have to do.
隐世狼女
第2季第6集
罗根
Logan?
Logan.
我在哪
Where am I?
你还好吗
You all right?
他们给我注射了别人的血液
They injected me with someone's blood.
他们给你注射了埃琳娜的血液吗
Did they inject you with Elena's blood?
那会让我变成狼吗
Would that turn me into a wolf?
我见到过她 罗根
I saw her, Logan!
他逼我看埃琳娜
He forced me to watch Elena.
她变成了狼
She became a wolf!
我可以跑掉 但是回头来找你了
I could've run but I came back for you,
所以请说实话
so just be honest!
你是他们其中之一 是吗
You're one of them, aren't you.
宝贝 听着 我不知道
Baby, listen. I don't know
他们给你注射了什么毒药
what kind of drugs they gave you...
别说谎 我应该更好的 我应该知道真相
Don't lie. I deserve better. I deserve the truth.
我一开始就该知道
I deserved it from the beginning.
我们在一起两年了
Two years we were together!
两年来 我爱你
Two years that I loved you,
而且这两年你也爱着我
and it's two years that you loved me back.
孩子呢
And the baby?
我怀着的是什么
What am I pregnant with?
听着 我们的孩子会有好多年
Listen, our child will have plenty of years
- 都很正常... - 正常
- of being normal before... - Normal?
然后呢
And then what?
然后他就会和他爸一样
And then he becomes like his father.
成为狼人
A werewolf.
你为什么没给我说过
Why didn't you tell me?
我该怎么向你解释
How am I going to explain that to you
能让你觉得我没疯
without you thinking I'm insane?
我该怎么给其他人说 你让我怎么做
How do I tell anybody that? What would you have me do?
我们要离开这
We're going to get out of here.
离开这儿以后
And when we do,
我不希望再见到你
I want you to walk away from me.
- 再试一次 - 我不行
- One more try. - I can't.
手放在上面
Picture your hand on top.
手掌在球上方慢慢感受
Feel the cool metal on your palm.
闭上眼
Close your eyes.
噢我做不到 对不起
Oh, I can't, I'm sorry.
这是一种伟大而古老的力量
This is a great and ancient power
我们生来就有
you and I possess.
没有护身符我没办法获得巫力
Without the talisman, I can't connect to the Coven.
很长时间来 我也没有护身符
For the longest time, I didn't have one either.
但我坚持下来了 你也可以
I survived. So will you.
这是你们巫师团控制你的另一种方式
It's another way for your Coven to control you.
她们爱我
They love me.
埃琳娜也这么说
Elena even said so.
我是锁
I am the lock.
我就是钥匙
And I am the key.
很好
Good.
那你为什么心烦意乱
Then why are you distracted?
埃琳娜还好吗
Is Elena okay?
为什么这么说
What makes you think she isn't?
我能感觉到她 她不太好
I can just... feel her. Something's not right.
我不想她出事
I don't want anything bad to happen to her.
埃琳娜对你没有影响
Elena has no influence on you.
你会忘了她说的话
You will forget what she said.
她不会出现在你脑海中
She is no longer in your mind.
她们想控制我
They want to control me.
你要是把床弄塌了
If you tear your bed apart,
就只能睡地板了
you'll just have to sleep on the floor.
你在意什么
What do you care?
什么也没有
I don't.
但萨凡纳是个心思敏感孩子
But Savannah is a sensitive girl.
因为某些原因 她越来越依赖你
And for some reason she's grown attached to you.
她总能感受到你在身边
She can feel you from across the compound
我希望她集中精神
and I need her to concentrate.
你有什么目的
For what?
毁灭
The Undoing.
我希望她平静下来
I want her to be calm
这就要求你必须先平静下来
which requires you to be calm.
你要失控了
You're losing control.
如果她能感受到我
If she can sense me,
那她就知道 我是不会让你成功的
then she knows that I won't let you go through with it.
你们狼人真是个
You werewolves are such an...
有趣的物种
interesting species.
哪种咒语下在你身上有用哪种没用
I wish I could spend more time figuring out
有时间的话真想让你尝个遍
which spells work on you and which don't.
最强大的狼人
The most powerful werewolf...
我不是最强大的
I'm not the most powerful.
要不是有人让我看到了 我都不知自己多强大
I didn't know how powerful I was until someone showed me.
世间唯一的男巫
The only male witch.
与唯一的狼女
The only female werewolf.
我们有很多地方是一样的
We have so much in common.
我们一点都不一样
We have nothing in common.
我想知道什么才能摧毁你
I wonder what it would take to break you?
也许你需要自我突破
Maybe you need to break yourself.
九界
Novem tibi orbibus.
很快就结束了
It will all soon be over.
好好享受
Enjoy your day.
魁北克省东方镇
森林面积三千英亩 有十条通路
There are 3,000 acres of forest and 10 access roads.
就是狼也没法及时搜索全面
Even as a wolf I couldn't search all this in time.
我们得找些当地人 也许他们知道它在哪儿
We can find some locals. Maybe they know where it is.
最近的小镇离这儿二十英里
The nearest town is 20 miles away.
我觉得 我们快来不及了
We're running out of time, I can feel it.
萨凡纳已经成年了
Savannah's passed into womanhood,
就像空气中的静电
it's like static electricity in the air.
你能顺着找到她吗
Can you follow it to her?
就像追逐一场雷暴
That would be like chasing a thunderstorm.
不会再来一次吧
Not again.
有事情发生了
Something's happening.
另一场仪式要开始了
There's going to be another ritual.
一定有法子离开这里
There's got to be some kind of way to get out of here.
万一我们就是祭品呢
What if we're the ritual?
什么
Wh... Like what?
他们在我身上做了全部测试
All the tests they've been doing on me.
他们不在乎我 他们关心的是孩子
They don't care about me, it's the baby they're after!
罗根 万一他们想拿走他怎么办
Logan, what if they want to take him?
喂 看着我 这是不会发生的好吗
Hey. Look at me. That's not going to happen, all right?
我没在开玩笑 我要疯了
I'm not joking, I'm losing my mind.
我不想死在这
I don't want to die down here.
那是什么
What's that?
我猜是割到电线了
Guess I clipped a wire.
嘘
Sh...
天呐
Oh, god...
你们巫师能和自然沟通
You witches with your talk of communing with nature,
难道不知道别穿高跟鞋进森林吗
you don't know enough not to wear heels in the forest.
我哪里有时间
It's not like I had time
去鞋店买鞋
to stop at a shoe store.
知道吗 我们面对的是更糟的事
We have worse to face too, you know,
比如我们会不会死
like whether or not we're all going to die.
你别想拖累我
You're not going to slow me down.
我不会等你的
I'm not stopping.
我得找到埃琳娜
I'm going to find Elena.
别傻了 你需要我在你身边
Don't be such a meathead. You need me with you.
我只需要埃琳娜给我信号
Elena will signal. That is all I need.
如果她没法给我们信号呢
What if she can't signal us?
她会给的
She will!
你对她有信心 这很好
You know, your confidence in her is really sweet,
但是 万一呢
but still. What if.
只要我们离使用魔法的人够近
Anyone who uses magic, if we're close enough,
通过这个我就能找出他们
I can spot them with this.
你需要我在你身边
You need me with you.
跟上我否则我就拽着你的头发上路
Keep up or I drag you by the hair.
我没法呼吸了
I can't breathe.
贴着门上的那个孔
Stay close to the holes in the door.
快脱掉你的胸罩
Your bra. Take it off!
你开什么玩笑
You kidding me?
- 快 - 你搞什么鬼
- Come on. - What are you doing?
我需要你胸罩里的铁丝 快给我
I need the wire! The wire in your bra, give it to me.
我们会逃出去的
We're going to get out of here.
埃琳娜
Elena.
亲爱的你安全了 我在你身边
I'm here, darling. You're safe.
克莱 你怎么找到我的
Clay, how did you find me?
无论你去世界上的哪个地方
There's no place in this world you can go
我都能找到你
where I won't find you.
杰里米还有其他人呢
Where are the others? Jeremy?
这里只有我们
It's just us.
我和你
You and me.
就像注定的那样
The way it's supposed to be.
我得走了...
I have to go...
别 别
No, no.
自我第一次见你 我就知道...
The first time I saw you...
我的所有一切都属于你
I knew every part of me belonged to you.
克莱...
Clay...
我咬你是为了给你我的一切
I bit you so you could have it all.
快啊...
Come on...
你能走吗
Can you walk?
- 我还跑的动 - 那就好
- I can run. - All right.
你看到什么东西了吗
Did you see anything?
可能吧 我看到东边有闪光
Maybe. I saw a glint in the east,
就在森林的深处
deeper into the forest.
但是一晃就不见了
But it was quick and then it was gone.
是魔法吗
Was it magic?
反正绝对不寻常
Oh, it was something.
告诉我准确的地点
Tell me exactly where.
告诉你干吗 你能干什么
Why, what are you going to do?
像猎狗一样跑来跑去
Run around like a bloodhound
到处乱嗅吗
sniffing for who-knows-what?
态度敢不敢再差一点
I don't think your attitude's very cute.
留些暴脾气给尼克吧
Save it for Nick.
我的意思是 我们二十分钟内就能赶到那里
I'm saying that we can make it there in 20 minutes.
我能看到魔力 就意味着有进入的通道
I saw power lines, which means an access road.
我能在地图找出它来
I can find it on the map.
感觉怎么样
What do you think?
我从没有过...
I've never had...
任何...
anything...
这么美的东西
like this before.
也该是时候了
Well, isn't it time?
所有东西都准备好了
Everything is ready.
所有人也都到了
Everyone is here
只为了给你庆祝 萨凡纳
to celebrate you, Savannah.
今天
Today,
你能掌控你的能力
you can use your powers.
今天就是毁灭的日子
Today is the day of the Undoing.
我希望埃琳娜能看到这些
I wish Elena could see it.
萨凡纳
Savannah!
戴安
Diane?
我哥哥
My brother,
他因你而死
he's dead because of you!
如今我也将步他的后尘
And now so am I.
我一定要找你报仇
I am coming for you.
这一切...
You...
是你造成的 埃琳娜
did this, Elena.
你会付出代价的
And you will pay!
这一切是你造成的 埃琳娜
You did this, Elena!
你会付出代价的
And you will pay!
You will pay!
你会付出代价的
You will pay.
你会... 付出... 代价
You... will... pay!
看这里
Over here.
萨凡纳
Savannah?
埃琳娜 你还好吗
Elena, are you okay?
我怎么知道你是真的
How do I know you're real?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我当然是... 真的
Okay, of course I'm... real.
我感觉到你有麻烦
I felt you were in trouble.
我就从亚雷斯塔那跑出来了
I got away from Aleister.
他对我动了手脚
He did something to me.
搅乱我的神智
Messing with my mind.
我知道
I know.
我们要离开这里
We need to get out of here.
跟着我 我 我知道怎么走
Follow me, I... I know the way.
杰里米说他们发现两百英里外的另一个
Jeremy said they found the other military base
军事基地 那里什么都没有
200 miles away. There's nothing there.
大楼紧锁 场地封闭了好些年
Buildings have been knocked to the ground years ago.
这里太安静了
It's quiet.
一定是在这附近某个地方
It's got to be somewhere around here.
秘密军事基地不可能这么简单就被找到
Hidden military bases aren't supposed to be easy to find.
如果我可以 我去做
If I could, I would,
但我不能四处飞着找
but I can't fly around
有红屋顶和薰衣草的地方
looking for red roofs and lavender.
总之 我们要找的是什么类型的信号
What type of signal are we looking for, anyway?
不管是什么类型的 越明显越好找
Whatever it is, it better be big.
我等不下去了
I can't take the waiting.
你真的很爱她 是吧
You really do love her, don't you.
比你想的还要爱
More than you can imagine.
我小时候就被教导要学会怎样独处
When I was a little girl, I was taught how to be alone.
怎样形影相吊 怎样自娱自乐
How to stay alone, how to be happy alone.
我曾经也是这样
I thought that way, once.
现在不是了
Not anymore.
我十三岁时 有个男孩
There was a boy, when I was 13.
他和我同住一条街
He lived on my street.
他叫杰夫
His name was Jeff.
还有比这个更无聊的名字了吗 "杰夫"
Is there a more boring name than that? "Jeff"?
他总是很安静
He was quiet.
害羞
Shy.
从不敢跟我说一句话
Never really said a word to me.
有一天
And then one day
我在信箱里找到绑头发的发带
I found this ribbon for my hair in the mailbox.
接下来又有另一个发带 之后每个星期都有
And then another one, and then one every single week.
发带很漂亮
They were beautiful ribbons.
然后我绑上这些发带走在街上
And I'd wear them and I'd walk down the street
我看到杰夫对我微笑
and I would see Jeff and he'd be smiling at me.
我觉得我要疯了
And then I felt like I was going crazy
因为这只让我想到
'cause all I could think about was the...
无聊的小子
boring kid.
在无聊的街上
On the boring street.
之后我拿到了这个
And then I got this.
做了个女巫
Became a witch.
再没有时间跟愿意
Didn't have any more time for boys
给我买发带的男生一起
who wanted to buy me ribbons for my hair.
我自己选择的
I made a choice.
该来的总会来
When it happens,
你也别无选择
you don't get a choice.
你不会再孤单了
You never want to be alone again.
我有我妈
I have my mother.
女巫团
My Coven.
我一点都不孤单
I am not alone.
走吧 罗密欧
Let's get going, Romeo.
我们会找到她的
We will find her.
我们为什么会在这
Why are we here?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
这不是出去的路
This isn't the way out of here.
有东西要你看看
You need to see something.
不 不
No... No...
这不可能
That's not possible.
一切都是假的
Nothing's real.
你还是困在牢笼里
You're still in your cell.
幻觉
Hallucinating.
你发不出信号给你的朋友
You can't signal your friends.
我知道我是真实的
I know I'm real.
你骗我
You lied to me.
你从来没有打算要帮我
You were never going to help me.
你只想着要逃出这里
You just wanted to get out.
不
No...
你只在乎你自己 埃琳娜
You only care about yourself, Elena.
逃不出自己的掌心
Can't escape your own mind.
自私
Selfish!
他们都会因你而死
They're all going to die because of you.
因你而死
For you.
求求你
Please...
别
Stop...
你就是个怪物
You are a monster!
你就该这样
And you deserve to suffer for it!
你就呆在这里
You are going to stay here...
永远
forever.
慢着 他们离开草坪了
Wait. They're heading out to the field.
我们得从树林那边穿过去
We have to go through the woods.
哦 不 不 不 我们不能走太远
Oh, no no no, we're not going to get far
如果这些鬼东西又开始沸腾起来
if these things start heating up again.
我们可以让他们停止行动
We can disable them.
这个不可见的封印
The entire invisible perimeter.
我们得去亚雷斯塔的房间
We have to get to Aleister's quarters.
在院子的另一边
It's on the other side of the compound.
我们走
Let's go.
埃琳娜 我们要做的只有离开
Elena. All we have to do is walk away
一切都会好起来的
and everything will be all right.
那里面有什么
What's down there?
安详
Peace.
你所寻找的安详
The peace you're looking for.
我辜负了萨凡纳
I failed Savannah.
我答应过要保护她
I promised I'd protect her.
跟我走吧
Come with me.
这都是为你好
It's for your own good.
你可以放下这一切
You can let it all go.
不
No.
我不想就这样一走了之
I don't want to let it go.
这不是我想要的
That's not what I want.
那你想要什么
Then what do you want?
爱
Love.
Love?
到最后 这才是最重要的
In the end, it's all that matters.
这才是关键
It is the key.
我们不是怪物
We're not monsters.
因为我们...
Because we...
我们能相爱
we can love?
你现在只能靠自己了
You're on your way back, now.
你会用到那些 亲爱的
You're going to need those, darling.
出去外面 向我示意
Get outside. Signal me.
...我们的信仰
...the one true path.
他是一道即将指引我们走向毁灭的光芒
He is the light that will guide us to the Undoing.
他是我们的信仰
He is the one true path.
他是一道即将指引我们走向毁灭的光芒
He is the light that will guide us to the Undoing.
向依然在我们心中的两位鞠躬
Bow before the two who shall remain.
聚集力量
Gather the power.
...毁灭
...the Undoing.
他是我们的信仰
He is the one true path.
他是一道即将指引我们走向毁灭的光芒
He is the light that will guide us to the Undoing.
他是我们的信仰
He is the one true path.
他是一道即将指引我们走向毁灭的光芒...
He is the light that will guide us to the Undoing...
停下
Stop!
给我那女孩
Give me the girl!
埃琳娜
Elena.
我要萨凡纳
I want Savannah.
现在
Now!
那不像是个仪式
Okay, that did not sound like a ritual.
我不在乎 赶紧离开这吧
I don't care. Let's just get out of here.
看 这就是能量所标记的东西
There. That's what powers these marks.
你应该提醒我
You know, you could've warned me.
瑞秋... 我爱你
Rachel... I love you.
好吧 对不起
All right? And I'm sorry,
我不是故意让事情变成这样的
I didn't mean for any of this to happen.
你回来找我
You came back for me.
这也算有点价值了
It counts for something.
我们赶紧离开这里吧
Let's just get out of here.
亚雷斯塔
Aleister!
去找埃琳娜和萨凡纳
Find Elena and Savannah.
剩下的我来解决
I'll take care of this.
萨凡纳
Savannah.
我们得走了
We have to go.
抱歉 埃琳娜
Sorry, Elena.
我试过反抗
I tried to resist.
但他太厉害了
But he's too strong.
他没有施放魔咒
He didn't do the spell.
他没有杀死那些女巫 我们可以离开
He didn't kill all of the witches. We can go.
我不能
I can't.
我得留下
I have to stay.
她们并不爱我
They don't love me.
她们想要控制我
They want to control me.
你不需要做别的
You don't have to do anything.
好吗 你只要...
Okay? Just...
跟我走 我们离开这 好吗
Come with me. We'll get out of here. Okay?
萨凡纳 你清楚你哪都不会去
Savannah, you know you aren't going anywhere.
斗争直到最后一刻
Fight to the end.
我很佩服
I'm impressed.
我希望我能够多跟你在一起
I wish I could've spent more time with you.
我想从你身上得到的一切都得到的
I have everything I need from you.
我不明白
I don't understand
你为什么这么在意这些女巫
why you would care so much about these witches.
不久前 你甚至不知道她们的存在
Not long ago, you didn't even know they existed.
没有她 我是不会走的
I'm not leaving here without her.
那真是太糟了
That's too bad.
这就是你的结局
This is how it ends for you.
佩吉
Paige!
放开萨凡纳
Let Savannah go!
佩吉
Paige.
我很高兴是你
I'm glad it's you.
我们从没好好地了解过彼此
We never got the chance to know each other.
我不想了解你
I don't want to know you.
这就是你跟你哥说话的方式
That's no way to talk to your big brother.
不
No.
不可能
It's not possible.
露丝・温特伯恩有一个儿子
Ruth Winterbourne had a son.
是我
Me.
你撒谎
You're lying.
她不想要我
She didn't want me.
现在她可以尝尝
But now she'll know the pain of
失去她在意的孩子的痛苦了
losing the child she did want.
啊 啊 啊 小心点
Ah-ah-ah, careful.
你攻击我 她会受伤的
You come at me, she might get hurt.
萨凡纳.
Savannah.
他的能量没你强
He doesn't have any power over you.
没人能够控制你
No one can control you.
让他们瞧瞧 萨凡纳
Show them who you trust, Savannah.
我就是锁
I am the lock.
萨凡纳 我就是锁
Savannah. I am the lock.
我是你的朋友
I am your friend.
佩吉
Paige!
没事了 萨凡纳
It's okay, Savannah.
我们在这
We have you.
你把亚雷斯塔传送到哪了
Where did you send Aleister?
我也不知道
I'm not sure.
成像
Imago.
我就是锁...
I am the lock...
那件事已经结束了
That thing is over!
除非我们离开这 快上来
Not until we're miles away from here. Get in.
罗根 这回
Logan! This time,
你得听我的 上车
you're going to do what I say. Get in!
埃琳娜在哪
Where's Elena?
她很好 她正带着萨凡纳过来
She's okay. She's taking Savannah to the car.
这是你干的
Did you do this?
是吧
I guess I did.
他死了
He's dead.
终于结束了
It's finally over.
我要找到埃琳娜
I need to find Elena.
克莱
Clay!
符号不见了
The symbol's gone.
我在哪里
Where am I?
你记得过去的事吗
Do you remember anything?
我在谢里丹公园喂鸽子
I was feeding pigeons in Sheridan Park,
和一个男人在说...
talking to a man...
哪个城市
What city?
这里不是奥尔巴尼吗
This isn't Albany?
发生了什么
What's happening?
我的天呐
Oh my God.
你们是谁
Who are you people?
发生了什么
What happened?
睡吧
Dormi.
他们都醒来的时候 我们就有麻烦了
We're going to have problems when they all wake up.
我能让他们一直睡
I can keep them sleeping.
如果他们在别的地方醒来
But it would be better if they could wake up
会好点
somewhere other than here.
好吧 我们最后再来调查
Okay, the last thing we need is
这里究竟发生了什么
an investigation into what happened here.
杰里米和尼克会在一小时后到
Jeremy and Nick will arrive in an hour.
让他们来把这些人弄走
They'll figure out how to get these people far away.
别让他们记起这发生了什么
Just as long as they don't remember any of this.
他们不会的
No, they won't.
我会看着他们的
I'll watch out for them!
睡吧
Dormi.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
你信守了你的承诺
You kept your promise.
我不想让我的朋友失望
I don't like letting my friends down.
埃琳娜 我们能做朋友吗
Elena, can we stay friends?
不是那种偶尔发发短信的那种
I don't mean texting each other every now and then.
我的意思是...
I mean...
我们可以经常见面
We actually can get to see each other.
我也如此
I'd like that.
埃琳娜
Elena!
哦 你没事...
Oh, you're safe...
你成功了
You made it.
没什么能阻止我
Nothing would've stopped me.
带我离开这 越远越好
Get me as far away from here as possible.
我带你回家 怎么样
I'll get you home, how about that.
他们有没有伤到你
Did they hurt you?
我看见了些东西 克莱
I saw things, Clay.
我几乎失去理智
I almost lost my mind.
我会在你身边的
I'll be here for you.
你一直都在
You always were.
这里没有瑞秋和罗根的迹象
There's no sign of Rachel and Logan.
他们肯定逃走了
They must've escaped.
那我们都安全了
Then we're all safe.